<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Antonio Jacob Martinez]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Antonio Jacob Martinez]]></description>
        <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:39:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:39:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biography]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Biography</strong></h1>,<p>Antonio Jacob Martinez is a fine art photographer, specializing in experimental photographic practices, as evidenced in his latest series, How to Hug and Other Sublimations of Men and previous project, Near the Egress. Both of these projects have been exhibited nationally and internationally and belong to permanent collections in national museums.</p>,<p>Antonio currently teaches a range of photography courses, analog and digital, at Southern Illinois University, located in Carbondale, IL.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1eb80278-619c-40fd-b2f6-e8d8bd4a846b.jpg">,<p>Antonio’s interests does not stop at photography. He is currently interested in incorporating quilt making and stained glass into his photographic work. </p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/98e20abc-9549-4afa-99b7-6dc47570e648.jpg">,<p>Antonio explores a variety of processes and camera formats, from 4x5 view cameras to DayLab polaroid lifts.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d318be89-c3ea-447c-9d3c-5865abc272b2.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/antonio-jacob-martinez-is-a-fine-art-photographer-specializ/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">04268a7c-39d8-4b6f-ba55-7585a7970e33</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 20:13:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Hug and Other Sublimations of Men]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>How to Hug and Other Sublimations of Men</h1>,<p>These expressive photographs capture moments between the exchange of pain and power between two men who display symbols of fearlessness and valor through their actions, but also on their skin and clothing apparel. The hand-applied surface abrasions and ink removal around the bodies of the athletes suggests both movement and men physically sublimating into something greater than what can be achieved outside the arena.</p>,<p>Having experienced my first cagefight last year, I gained a greater appreciation for what it means to experience life on a more physical level when compared to my daily activities as a professor in a classroom. As a professor, the pursuit of enriching the mind through observation and study, without firsthand physical experience, became the path to knowledge. I needed more than to speculate and to observe as an uninitiated outsider; I w anted firsthand experience in pursuing a physical challenge that seemed both admirable and deplorable.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/886612e0-a47a-405a-80fe-180c22503c81.jpg" title="How to Hug and Other Sublimations of Men">]]></description>
            <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/fa14be47-fc5d-4eec-af55-8fa5f1cebac8/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fa14be47-fc5d-4eec-af55-8fa5f1cebac8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Freeport Museum Offers Different Takes On Masculinity]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Freeport Museum Offers Different Takes On Masculinity</h1><p>The Freeport Art Museum &apos;s current exhibit is called &quot;The Nature of Masculinity.&quot; Tommy Reyes co-curated &quot;The Nature of Masculinity.&quot; He&apos;s an artist and the owner of Gallery 19 in Chicago, and a member of the arts group the Exhibition Project.</p><img src="http://mediad.publicbroadcasting.net/p/wnij/files/styles/medium/public/201606/martinez_grapplers.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/freeport-museum-offers-different-takes-on-masculinity/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">76b909c6-432e-49af-80b6-c7c5e32a1e6b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 15:34:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0c651d6f-37c5-48f1-8eac-a910257a2186.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/1a12e609-8822-4102-9547-0e29f9f2d109/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1a12e609-8822-4102-9547-0e29f9f2d109</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE MALE GAZE ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2><strong>THE MALE GAZE </strong></h2>,<p>A small selection of images from the How to Hug and Other Sublimations of Men series was featured in two exhibitions a the Seattle-based gallery. The first exhibit was entitled the Male Gaze, which is a twist on the traditional feminist interpretation of the “male gaze.</p>,<p><a href="http://www.gallery1of1.com/Exhibit_Detail.cfm?ShowsID=83" title="The Male Gaze">Click to see examples from the Male Gaze Exhibition</a></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7b9421aa-6481-4358-af86-a4a46d5a7e49.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://antoniojacobmartinez.com/near-the-egress-by-antonio-martinez/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5f6640-89dd-445a-b6cc-a378082b539d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 20:00:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>